Jennifer Green, JD UX Designer & Writer

New York, NY | +16176998279 jengreen88@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/jenniferagreen/ www.jagwd.com

CAREER OBJECTIVE

UX writer and designer with a background in financial compliance and law, blending design thinking and user-centered language to craft purposeful user experiences. My deep knowledge of written communication and regulatory compliance will contribute to the growth of an organization by bringing my design, writing, and exceptional team-building skills to any environment.

SKILLS

- · Figma, HTML, Miro, Adobe XD, Slack, Microsoft Office Suite, Google workspace
- · Writing, wireframing, prototyping, responsive web design, user research analysis
- · Rapport-building, negotiating, strategic thinking

UX PROJECTS

- · UX Designer, Researcher, and Writer
 - "Expert" responsive web app prototype.
 - Competitor analysis, user testing, end-to-end design and copy writing
 - Figma, Miro, Lucidchart
 - o "Flashcards are Fun!" flashcard app prototype
 - Competitor analysis, end-to-end design and copy writing
 - Marvel
- UX Writer
 - o Toasts, pop-ups, 404 messages, error messages, and push notifications.
 - Figma

LICENSES & CERTIFICATIONS

- · Introduction to UX Design Career Foundry
- UX Immersion Career Foundry
- · **UX Writing** *UX Writing Hub In progress*
- Robotic Process Automation Level 1 UiPath
- · Licensed Attorney Massachusetts and Connecticut

EXPERIENCE

Freelance Designer

2023 - Present

New York, NY

- Designed responsive web app from end-to-end.
- Conducted competitor analysis and user testing.
- Applied feedback to each iteration of the wireframe and prototype in Figma creating an
 effective app for users to connect with experts in a myriad of industries.

Various global financial institutions and banks, New York, NY

Policies & Procedures

- Enhanced employee compliance knowledge by creating compliance policy and procedure chatbot, resulting in decreased calls to the compliance helpline.
- Met regulatory mandates for wealth management documentation by managing the annual review of over 300 policies and procedures in partnership with document owners and SMEs.
- Managed a team of writers to compose over 600 business narratives for high-risk banking customers resulting in a swift conclusion to a remediation project.

Contract Management

- Established contract database by analyzing financial vendor contracts using deep knowledge in law, compliance, and risk; worked with vendors to update agreements.
- · Drafted intermediary fund participation, shareholder servicing, and distribution-related contracts in consultation with Sales, Legal, Risk, Operations, and Compliance teams

Policy Implementation Manager

2015 - 2016

Bank of America, New York, NY

- Ensured timely annual review of 800 wealth management policies across 10 business units, including alternative investments, retirement, trusts, and credit & lending, by establishing a review schedule and weekly approval meeting.
- Managed web administrators in India responsible for uploads to the policy library
- Collaborated with IT to streamline policy management tools, upgrade templates, and perform user acceptance testing (UAT)
- Orchestrated architectural improvements to the digital policy library and implemented an enhanced SharePoint site

Estate Settlement Officer

2012 - 2015

Bank of America, New York, NY

- Conducted the settlement of trust and estate assets for high net worth clients (\$2MM \$150MM)
- · Coordinated corporate dissolutions by collaborating with trust officers, portfolio managers, and external legal counsel
- Conducted a complete marshalling of decedent assets by managing the research of asset claims and settlements in foreign countries, ensuring FATCA compliance
- · Instructed estate/trust team on latest technology developments by serving on the Digital Assets Policy Team

KYC Officer 2011 - 2012

Bank of New York Mellon, New York, NY

Associate Attorney, Estate Planning and Probate

2009 - 2011

Eckert Byrne, LLC

EDUCATION

- Juris Doctor Massachusetts School of Law
- Master of Technical & Professional Writing Northeastern University
- Bachelor of Arts Syracuse University, English and Textual Studies